# **Gary Tang**

E: nguyen.ktang@gmail.com | W: garykntang.com linkedin.com/in/nguyenktang | P: 0468 593 404

Adelaide SA Australia

#### **SUMMARY**

UX/UI Designer with a background in Psychology. Have 7 years of experience in retail and customer service. Highly interested in human cognition, perception, and behaviour. Strengths in doing research, quick to adapt and always eager to learn. Looking to build a career in the tech industry.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

**UX/UI:** User Research, Prototyping, Usability Testing, User Flow, Information Architecture, Interaction Design. **Tools:** Adobe Creative Suite, Figma, Invision, RStudio, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python.

### **PROJECTS**

**INFLOW** *Mental health mobile app* | https://bit.ly/3tNVzuv

Responsibilities: user research, user flow, competitor analysis, usability tests, prototyping.

**STORY DOGS** Not-for-profit organization website redesign | <a href="https://bit.ly/3sStjqd">https://bit.ly/3sStjqd</a>

Responsibilities: user research, user flow, usability tests, information architecture redesign.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## **UX/UI DESIGNER – FRONTEND DEVELOPER** Freelance | Adelaide, SA

APR 2021 - PRESENT

- Have been working on four elearning projects (LMS).
- Conducting user research to inform design decisions.
- Turning mockups into responsive websites using HTML and CSS.
- Working in a team with other UI designers and developers.

## **CUSTOMER SERVICE OFFICER** *Datacom* | Adelaide, SA

JUL 2021 - DEC 2021

- Providing essential services to the public.
- Answering more than 50 customers' enquiries per day.
- Making detail notes after every call in a timely manner.

## **EDUCATION**

Certificate IV of IT | 42 Adelaide FEB 2022 – PRESENT

Certificate in UX/UI | University of Adelaide AUG 2020 – MAR 2021

Bachelor of Psychological Science | University of Adelaide FEB 2015 – FEB 2020

## **LANGUAGES**

**English** – Fluent | **Vietnamese** – Native | **Japanese** + **Mandarin** + **Cantonese** – Conversational